Byungwoo Jeon

50, Sinchon-ro 28-gil, Seoul, Republic of Korea

📕+82 10 33641362 | 🗷 ipcs@korea.ac.kr | 🛠 rootyjeon.github.io/ | 🖸 github.com/rootyJeon | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/byungwoo-jeon

Research Interest

My research goal is to build a representation of the 3d world so that it can be used in real-time for real-world problems. To this end, I focus on (i) how to effectively reduce the computation and memory cost of 3d data and (ii) how to understand primitives in general in terms of neural networks.

- Self-supervised and Contrastive Learning
- Neural Radiance Fields
- Generative Models

Education

Korea University Seoul, Korea

B.S. in Computer Science & Engineering, Statistics (Double Major)

Mar 2020 - Current

Experience ____

Algorithmic Intelligence Lab (ALINLAB), KAIST AI

Jeongja, Korea

Undergraduate Intern (advisor: Prof. Jinwoo Shin)

Mar 2023 - Current

- · Researched Self-supervised Learning on Label-free and Zero-shot Tasks
- Researched Depth Estimation with Neural Radiance Fields

ARCREAL Gangnam, Korea

Research Intern (host: Prof. Jinwoo Shin)

Jan 2023 - Current

- Developed AI systems for medical equipment
- Developed segmentation projects
- Researched several 3d vision topics

LIM Lab, Korea Univ. STAT Anam, Korea

Undergraduate Intern (advisor: Prof. Sungbin Lim)

Aug 2023 - Current

· Researched Diffusion models with Genesis Lab

Machine Learning & Vision Lab (MLVLAB), Korea Univ. CSE

Anam, Korea Jul 2022 - Dec 2022

Undergraduate Intern (advisor: Prof. Hyunwoo J. Kim)

- · Studied Open-Vocabulary Object Detection
- Studied Human-Object Interaction (HOI)
- Participated in the government policy supporting AI challenge team
- Participated in the MLVLAB weekly group paper study (Paper reading & Implementation)

M-Monstar Pangyo, Korea

Full-stack Developer

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

- Developed a modular e-commerce management platform page using Laravel framework
- Optimized and debugged the site, HAGO

Honors & Awards

Artificial Intelligence Grand Challenge

Seoul, Korea

Top 9 (8^{th} Prize)

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

- Developed AI for supporting the government policies based on natural language proceessing
- · Developed query parser for pre-processing

Training₋

United Collegiate Programming Contest

Seoul, Korea

3 Problems solved

Yonsei-NAVER CLOUD Data Science Course

Seoul, Korea

Completed financial engineering course

Feb 2021 - Jun 2021

August 13, 2023



Programming Python (PyTorch, TensorFlow), C, C++, SQL, PHP, Javascript, R, SAS, Rust

Miscellaneous Linux, Firebase, Git, LTFX

Soft Skills Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Engaging Presentation.

Extracurricular Activity _____

KUBIG

Member Jul 2023 - Jul 2024

- · Participated in Computer Vision Seminar
- Participated in Time Series Analysis Seminar
- Participated as a pacemaker in Deep Learning Session of Professor Sungbin Lim, Korea Univ.

Google Developer Students Club

Lead Jul 2022 - Aug 2023

- Lectured Machine Learning, Databases, and Algorithm courses for undergraduate students
- Developed stable diffusion crawling with text summarization project
- Developed 2023 Google Solution Challenge project (digiHow)
- Lead three teams to the Global Top 100 in 2023 Google Solution Challenge
- Lead one team to the Global Top 10 in 2023 Google Solution Challenge
- Host of 2023 East Asia GDSC Global Hackathon in Tokyo

Korea Computer Science Academy (Academy club in Korea Univ.)

Member & Instructor

Mar 2020 - Mar 2022

- Lectured Data Structure course for undergraduate students
- Lectured C Programming course for undergraduate students

Languages

English Professional proficiency **Korean** Native proficiency

Coursework_

2023-1 Computer Vision

2023-1 Statistical Data Science

2020-1	Fundamentals of Data Science	
2020-2	Computer Programming	
2020-2	Linear Algebra	
2020-2	Data Structure	
2021-1	Algorithm	
2021-1	Theory of Computation	
2021-1	Discrete Mathematics	
2021-2	Databases	A+, Second-place
2021-2	Computer Network	
2021-2	Computer Architecture	
2022-1	Statistical Mathematics	
2022-1	Introduction to Probability Theory	
2022-1	Operating Systems	
2022-1	Artificial Intelligence	A+
2022-2	Machine Learning	A+
2022-2	Deep Learning	A+
2022-2	Regression Analysis	
2022-2	Probability and Random Process	
2023-1	Analysis	
2023-1	Natural Language Processing	A+

August 13, 2023 2

A+

A+, First-place